Ezz Elden Mohamed

Front-End Developer

El Mansoura , El Dakahleya | <u>+201002368023</u>|
<u>ezzelden4work@gmail.com</u>

My WebSite, linkedin , codepen , GitHub , Youtube

Summary

I've been working as front-end developer since I was a student. With 5 years of experience under my belt & 10s of successful projects, I manage to develop my skills to a high level & still eager to learn & develop my knowledge. I'm looking for a challenging job in the field where I can utilize my skills & gain more experience & develop my career.

Education

Bachelor degree in management information systems 2022

Skills

Html | css | Javascript | jQuery | BootStrap | Sass | Next.js | React.js | React Native | GitHub | CssAnimation | AdobeXD | Figma | Php | WordPress

Professional Experience

Code Time

Sep 2022 - Present

Front-end Web Developer & Team Leader

Responsibilities

- Team Leader For the Technology team
- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Optimize applications for maximum speed

Buraq

Sep 2022 - Dec 2021

• Front-end Web Developer

Responsibilities

- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Optimize applications for maximum speed

Sample projects:

- Twision
- Shams Store
- Todo pazer

<u>Atheltree</u>

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

• Front-end Web Developer

I design websites and make their user experience easier, then convert them into a live website

Responsibilities

- Apply newest techniques in front-end development and use most updated tools
- Using project management software to track and report on projects
- Optimize applications for maximum speed
- Make The UI and UX for the website and code it by front-end Languages

Sample projects:

- Survey
- Round Base

Web Development Instructor:

2021

Delivering Web development courses to groups of students from scratch to Profession.

Graduation projects Assistant:

2021

Assisting groups of students deliver their graduation projects by supervising all the project activities.

Sample projects:

Elfahd Elevetor

- Smart Parking
- Elkepash

The Lean

Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

Front-end Web Developer

I was converting the design from a static image to a live website that can be dealt with

Responsibilities

- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Optimize applications for maximum speed
- Consulting with the design team

Sample projects:

- Store Demo
- Youssef Allam Group
- Khozam

Afro Arab Digital

Feb 2020 - July 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

I was converting the design from a static image to a live website that can be dealt with

Sample projects:

- Afro Arab Digital
- Bakkahlean

Devolum

Oct 2017 - Feb 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

I was converting the design from a static image to a live website that can be dealt with

Responsibilities

- Translate UI/UX design wireframes to actual code
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- Optimize applications for maximum speed

Sample projects:

- Alemnishokran
- Midstr

- Islah
- Oral

Projects

Vuesax Dashboard gitHub Live View

- Dark & Light Mode
- Chat Page

Round Base <u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- React.js
- Company Review

Elkebash Site <u>Live View</u>

- WordPress
- Ui/Ux

See More Projects.....

Langues

Arabic : Native | English : Good Write and Speak